[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":119539,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":138285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":8892,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":147177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":9999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":157176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2397,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":159573,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":165084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1878,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":166962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["6","0"],"rt":9692,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":176654,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1164,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":177818,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3371,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":181189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub>  1 = 2 be cause 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1170,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":182359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3403,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":185762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":2028,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":187790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with  the fir st number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3668,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":191458,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1013,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":192471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":195943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":196870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2655,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":199525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":801,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":200328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":203355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":964,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":204329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, y ou subtr act 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2834,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":207163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1243,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":208406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":17424,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":225830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":41317,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":267147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7466,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":274623,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1603,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":276226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":280174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":957,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":281131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the i nverse o f 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":283868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":897,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":284765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2694,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":287459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":967,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":288426,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3233,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":291659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":46206,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":337875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":14840,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":352725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br />< br /> Ho wever, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":69097,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":421822,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":8102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":429924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2106,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":432030,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10 -0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":439573,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":17962,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":457535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<s ub>6</su b>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":34335,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":491870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":14314,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":506184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":10404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":516588,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2175,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":518766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accuratel y as pos sible.","rt":19138,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":537904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":9490,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":547394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1200,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":548604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4871,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":553475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5008,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":558483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":13017,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":571500,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4741,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":576241,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":580169,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. I added 4 and 1 and since the answer was below 9 I stopped there.","response_history":["5. I added 5","5. I added 4 and 1 and since the answer was below 9 I stopped there."],"rt":30060,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":610229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. I added 8 and 4 then since the answer was above 8 I subtracted 9.","response_history":["3. I added 8 and 4 then since it ","3. I added 8 and 4 then since it","3. I added 8 and 4 then since i","3. I added 8 and 4 then since ","3. I added 8 and 4 then sinceth","3. I added 8 and 4 then sincet","3. I added 8 and 4 then si nce the  answere","3. I added 8 and 4 then since the answer was above 8 I subtracted 9."],"rt":27871,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":638100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0. I'm not really certain why, I didn't understand that part.","response_history":["0. I'm not really certi","0. I'm not really certain why, I didn't understand that part."],"rt":39197,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":677307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":15666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":692973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 2-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4138,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":697111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4424,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":701535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. I looked at what would be needed to add to 3 to get 9.","response_history":["6. I subtracted 3 from ","6. I sub","6. I su","6. I s","6. I looked at what would be needed to add to 3 to get 9."],"rt":29821,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":731356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2 = 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2 = 6, 2+2+2+2 = 8, 2+2+2+2+2=10-9=1, etc.","response_history":["Yes, because ","No ","No, because you cannot add 2s together to ","No,","No","N","Yes, because you can add 2s together to get every other","Yes, because you can add 2s together to g","Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2+2","Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2+","Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2 = 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2 = 6, 2+2=","Yes, because you can add 2s together  to end u p with every other number between 0 and 8. 2 = 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2 = 6, 2+2+2+2+2 =","Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2 = 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2 = 6, 2+2+2+2+2 ","Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2 = 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2 = 6, 2+2+2+2+2","Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2 = 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2 = 6, 2+2+2+2+","Yes, because you can add 2s together to end up with every other number between 0 and 8. 2 = 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2 = 6, 2+2+2+2 = 8, 2+2+2+2+2=10-9=1, etc."],"rt":223696,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":955052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. 3 can make 0, 3, and 6, but not 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, and 8.","response_history":["No. S","No. You","No. Yo","No. Y","No. 3 can make 3, 6, ","No. 3 can make -3, 6, ","No. 3 can make 3, 6, ","No. 3 can make 03, 6, ","No. 3 can make 0,3, 6, ","No. 3 can make 0, 3, 6, but not 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, and 8.","No. 3 can make 0, 3, a6, but not 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, and 8.","No. 3 can make 0, 3, an6, but not 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, and 8.","No. 3 can make 0, 3, and6, but not 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, and 8.","No. 3 can make 0, 3, and 6, but not 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, and 8."],"rt":116970,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1072032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. I counted increments of 5 and kept subtracting 5. By the time I got to 45 I had all the numbers between 0 and 8.","response_history":["Yes. 5 can be added t","Yes. 5s can be added together ","Yes. I counted increm ents of  5 and kept subtracting 5. By the time I got to 45 I had all the numbers between 1 and 8.","Yes. I counted increments of 5 and kept subtracting 5. By the time I got to 45 I had all the numbers between 0 and 8."],"rt":199653,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1271685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I counted increments of 6 and subtracted 9, after about 4 increments it started generating the same numbers again. It can only generate 0, 3, and 6.","response_history":["No. I counted increments of 6 and subtracted 9, after about 4 increments it started generating the same numbers aa","No. I counted increments of 6 and subtracted 9, after about 4 increments it started generating the same numbers again. It can only generate 0, 3, and 6."],"rt":79066,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1350751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":18068,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1368819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n - 1","response_history":["n - 1"],"rt":41814,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1410633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>?  Please e xplain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n - x. The inverse is whatever needs to be added to x to equal n.","response_history":["n - x. The inves","n - x. The inverse is whatever n ","n - x. The inverse is whatever n","n - x. The inverse is whatever ","n - x. The inverse is whatever needs to be added to x to equal n."],"rt":51106,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1461739,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"If it's a multiple of 3 I think it probably is never a generator. If it's a multiple of 5 I think it always is. Beyond that I'm not really sure.","response_history":["If it's a multiple o f 3 I th ink it probably is nee","If it's a multiple of 3 I think it probably is never a generator. If it's a multiple of 5 I think it always is. Beyond that I'm not really sure."],"rt":98738,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1560477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":11726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1572213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1577668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":13156,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1590834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True. If x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers.","response_history":["If x ","If x","If x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end  up with  the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to geen","If x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to gee","If x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers","TIf x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers","TrIf x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers","TruIf x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers","TrueIf x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end u p with t he same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers","True.If x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers","True. If x is a multiple of n then when you're subtracting n you're always going to end up with the same pattern of numbers and will never be able to generate all the numbers."],"rt":81208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1672042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":25776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1697818,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14 -0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes. It depends on whether the inverse is a multiple/divisor of n. ","response_history":["Sometimes. It depends on whether the inves","Sometimes. It depends on whether the inverse is a multiple/divisor of n. "],"rt":33539,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1731357,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":32144,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1763501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1756,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1765257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"35","response_history":["35"],"rt":2705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1767962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2734,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1770696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any specific subject. ","response_history":["N","I took a curriculu, ","I took a curriculu,","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, a","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, ","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig,","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discrete math","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discrete mat","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discrete ma","I took a curri culum th at was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discrete m","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discrete s","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discrete ","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discrete","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discret","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discre","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any discr","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any disc","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any dis","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any di","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any d","I took a cu rriculum  that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any specific subt","I took a curriculum that was a combination of trig, algebra, etc. rather than any specific subject. "],"rt":144356,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1915052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1918917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of  it","2  - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4291,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1923208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1927039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - s omewhat"],"rt":3204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1930243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2707,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1932950,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1935157,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Engli sh","response_history":["English"],"rt":4155,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1939312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3517,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1942829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"My head hurts now but still I kind of enjoyed this.","response_history":["My head hurts now but still I kind of enjoyed this."],"rt":12660,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1955489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]